accreditedonlinecolleges.com 2018-01-26

# Privacy Policy - AccreditedOnlineColleges.com

## Terms of Use and Privacy Policy for Use of AccreditedOnlineColleges.com (Effective Date 2/5/2016)

Thank you for visiting AccreditedOnlineColleges.com. We appreciate your interest in our website content and services. Please take a moment to read through the page and familiarize yourself with the conditions governing the use of our website. You will learn how AccreditedOnlineColleges.com gathers and applies different types of information in order to bring you content and related products and services.

By visiting our website, we assume you agree to these Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. 

### Future Term & Policy Changes

We may revise our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy in the future. Therefore, it is a good idea to periodically revisit this page for the most up to date practices concerning your privacy and other important information.

## Cookies

We use cookies, and by using this website, you acknowledge and consent to our use of cookies. What are cookies? Cookies are small pieces of data sent from a website and stored in the user’s web browser, commonly for technical purposes such as web analytics. We perform our web analytics using Google Analytics, a Google, Inc. tool ([Learn more](http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html) about Google Analytics).

Advertising cookies do not contain personally identifiable information, so users are still anonymous. Their purpose is to allow advertisers to make ads more relevant to the user’s interests. Advertising cookies — sometimes referred to as third-party cookies — track navigation and publish ads on behalf of third parties.

### How We Use Cookies

We use cookies through services and partnerships with vendors and third party service providers. They help us with the following:

  * Web Analytics: We capture demographic and other anonymous data for web optimization and other analysis
  * Lead Auditing: This helps ensure the accuracy, relevancy and also the validity of information that users provide for us
  * Tracking Marketing and Conversion: This includes (but is not limited to), targeting and optimizing digital ad serving to improve relevance, the user experience, and advertising effectiveness

### Removing Cookies

You can remove cookies at any time through your browser. You may have to do this on a regular basis. Check the settings on your web browser for specifics. You can generally opt out of receiving personalized ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) or those who follow the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles, as well as from other third party advertisers and ad networks. You can also unsubscribe by visiting the opt-out pages on the NAI website and DAA websites.

## What We Collect

**Submitted Information:** Users submit personal contact information via our web forms. This includes name, telephone number, mailing address and email address.

Users voluntarily submit information to AccreditedOnlineColleges.com because they are requesting information on an educational product or service. We collect the submitted information, store it and then share it with schools and other third parties, so they can to provide the requested information about schools, programs and education-related services. 

When you voluntarily submit information to us, you authorize AccreditedOnlineColleges.com and our affiliated schools and partners to contact you by telephone, text messages, email or mail. This is in accordance with all applicable laws, regarding education options or related topics.

### Email Opt-Out

If you receive any email communications from us, a school, or third party that you do not want, you will be afforded the ability to opt-out of future mailings via a link in the email.

**Automatic Information:** When you visit AccreditedOnlineColleges.com, we receive and store certain types of anonymous information. We do this so we can make site improvements as well as to create a more relevant user experience. We use cookies to collect this anonymous data. This includes information such as your browser version, operating system version, and your IP address, among other things. This data is collected for the purpose of analytics, site optimization and for tailored advertising and marketing purposes.

By using this website, we assume you acknowledge and agree that the information we collect on our website may be shared with schools, affiliated companies, and third parties. This is done for the purpose of providing you with degree information, as well as to inform you of other programs and education-related products and services. By this acknowledgement, you also agree with our right to release any collected information, personally identifiable or otherwise, as needed, to businesses providing administration services for our company, such as email service delivery

When you submit personal information to AccreditedOnlineColleges.com, you grant permission for us, our affiliated entities, including schools, third party marketing partners and vendors to contact you via telephone, text messages, email, or mail. We will contact you for the purpose of providing information, marketing or otherwise, for education-related services and products.

The submitting of information also gives us, our affiliates, and our partners and vendors, the right to contact you and relinquishes any rights granted to you by the Do Not Call list or other applicable laws, for a period of time. The voluntary submission of information effectively omits Do Not Call requirements established by state and federal governments and may also provide exemption for us from other applicable laws. We can also release your personal information, for example to abide by a subpoena or other legal procedure, or in other instances required by law. AccreditedOnlineColleges.com can utilize this option when, in good faith, we believe it is necessary to preserve our rights, ensure the safety of you or others, explore alleged fraud, or to reply to a government or legal request, and/or in the instance that AccreditedOnlineColleges.com enters into a merger, acquisition, or sale of some or all of its assets to a third party.

## Contact Us

çIf you have any questions or concerns about our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, please contact us via our web contact form.
